rpgmaker.net 2019-12-31

# rpgmaker.net

### Privacy Guidelines

This privacy policy covers the information provided to and gathered by RPG Maker Network.

### Personal Information

We gather the following types of information:

  * Information provided by you - Some sections of rpgmaker.net allow you to enter publicly displayed personal information, including but not limited to your name and email address. You can choose not to provide this information.
  * Information gathered automatically - Certain types of information can be gathered automatically when you visit, including your IP address.

The site and its services are intended for adult audiences, and rpgmaker.net does not knowingly collect any personal information from anyone under 13 years of age.

### Disclosure

Your information may be available to administrators of rpgmaker.net. We will not disclose your personal information to any third parties, except:

  * when required by law to do so;
  * in connection with any legal proceedings;
  * in order to establish, exercise or defend our legal rights

### Security of your personal information

No sensitive personal information is handled directly by this website. All credit card and other financial transactions are processed entirely by a secure third party (in this case, PayPal), and your financial details are not made available to rpgmaker.net.

### Your rights

You can choose not to provide the voluntary information requested by this site, and your browser has options to prevent the use of cookies.

### Third-party websites

rpgmaker.net may provide links to third-party websites. We do not provide any identifiable or sensitive information to these sites.
